https://api.blooket.com/api/games?gameId=[Redacted]

{"playCount":[Redacted],"favoriteCount":[Redacted],"private":[Redacted],"questions":[{"question":"A horizontal row of elements in the periodic table","answers":["semiconductors (metalloids)","metals","period","atomic number"],"correctAnswers":["period"],"timeLimit":15,"random":true,"number":3},{"question":"Elements that have properties of both metals and nonmetals","answers":["ion","nonmetals","halogens","semiconductors (metalloids)"],"correctAnswers":["semiconductors (metalloids)"],"timeLimit":15,"random":true,"number":2},{"question":"A vertical column of elements in the periodic table; elements in a group share chemical properties.","answers":["atomic number","noble gas","group/family","periodic"],"correctAnswers":["group/family"],"timeLimit":15,"random":true,"number":4},{"question":"something that happens at regular intervals","answers":["periodic","valence electrons","metals","period"],"correctAnswers":["periodic"],"timeLimit":15,"random":true,"number":1},{"question":"Elements of group 2 of the periodic table: Beryllium, Magnesium, Calcium, Strontium, and Radium.","answers":["periodic","alkali earth metals","semiconductors (metalloids)","atomic mass"],"correctAnswers":["alkali earth metals"],"timeLimit":15,"random":true,"number":6},{"question":"A group of non-reactive gases (group18) on the periodic table.","answers":["noble gas","valence electrons","periodic","alkali metals"],"correctAnswers":["noble gas"],"timeLimit":15,"random":true,"number":8},{"question":"Number of protons and neutrons found within the nucleus of an atom","answers":["alkali earth metals","atomic mass","periodic","metals"],"correctAnswers":["atomic mass"],"timeLimit":15,"random":true,"number":9},{"question":"Elements that are good conductors of electric current and heat.","answers":["transition metals","ion","metals","alkali metals"],"correctAnswers":["metals"],"timeLimit":15,"random":true,"number":12},{"question":"Group I on the periodic table. One valence electron that is easily removed to form a POSITIVE IONS. Highly reactive.","answers":["semiconductors (metalloids)","alkali metals","halogens","nonmetals"],"correctAnswers":["alkali metals"],"timeLimit":15,"random":true,"number":5},{"question":"Groups 3-12","answers":["valence electrons","periodic","noble gas","transition metals"],"correctAnswers":["transition metals"],"timeLimit":15,"random":true,"number":10},{"question":"Number of protons in an atom's nucleus","answers":["group/family","periodic","halogens","atomic number"],"correctAnswers":["atomic number"],"timeLimit":15,"random":true,"number":11},{"question":"Elements of group 17. Have a charge of -1. Fluorine, Chlorine, Bromine, Iodine. Form compounds with sodium in the form NaX.","answers":["alkali earth metals","alkali metals","period","halogens"],"correctAnswers":["halogens"],"timeLimit":15,"random":true,"number":7},{"question":"An atom or group of atoms that has a positive or negative charge.","answers":["atomic mass","group/family","ion","halogens"],"correctAnswers":["ion"],"timeLimit":15,"random":true,"number":15},{"question":"elements that are poor conductors of heat and electricity","answers":["nonmetals","periodic","transition metals","alkali earth metals"],"correctAnswers":["nonmetals"],"timeLimit":15,"random":true,"number":13},{"question":"Electrons in the outermost energy level of an atom that are typically involved in chemical reactions by being gained, lost, or shared in the formation of chemical bonds.","answers":["atomic mass","alkali earth metals","valence electrons","atomic number"],"correctAnswers":["valence electrons"],"timeLimit":15,"random":true,"number":14}],"_id":"[Redacted]","title":"Periodic Table","author":"[Redacted]","desc":"[Redacted]","date":"[Redacted]","__v":0}

Chest ESP XPaths:

Div & Img
//*[@id="app"]/div/div/div[2]/div[2]/div[1]/img
//*[@id="app"]/div/div/div[2]/div[2]/div[2]/img
//*[@id="app"]/div/div/div[2]/div[2]/div[3]/img

Just Div
//*[@id="app"]/div/div/div[2]/div[2]/div[1]
//*[@id="app"]/div/div/div[2]/div[2]/div[2]
//*[@id="app"]/div/div/div[2]/div[2]/div[3]

Hid. Reward
//*[@id="app"]/div/div/div[2]/div[3]/div[2]
//*[@id="app"]/div/div/div[2]/div[3]/div[4]
//*[@id="app"]/div/div/div[2]/div[3]/div[6]

Chesp ESP Command:
document.getElementsByTagName("body").innerHTML="<style>
[@id=\"app\"]/div/div/div[2]/div[2]/div[1],[@id=\"app\"]/div/div/div[2]/div[2]/div[2],[@id=\"app\"]/div/div/div[2]/div[2]/div[3] {
     visibility:hidden;display:none;
}[@id=\"app\"]/div/div/div[2]/div[3]/div[2],[@id=\"app\"]/div/div/div[2]/div[3]/div[4],[@id=\"app\"]/div/div/div[2]/div[3]/div[6] {
     visibility:visible;display:block;
}
</style>"

[+] FOR 'styles__chest___3wN6v-camelCase'
https://www.blooket.com/main~3233b45b.7bbf347005905c6d0448.js?4c03fbbeda027c4e2c88

To Kick User From Lobby:

requests.delete(f"https://api.blooket.com/api/firebase/client?id={gamePin}&name={name}",headers={"Referer":"https://www.blooket.com/"})

API URL To Join Lobby:

https://api.blooket.com/api/firebase/join

API URL TO STEAL GOLD:

To set score: PUT https://www.blooket.com/api/firebase/setval, {"path":"GAME_ID/c/NAME","val":{"b":"ANIMAL_PIC","g": AMOUNT}}
To swap score: PUT https://www.blooket.com/api/firebase/setval, {"path":"GAME_ID/c/NAME","val":{"b":"ANIMAL_PIC","g": AMOUNT, at: "OTHER_PLAYER:ANIMAL_PIC:AMOUNT"}}
pics=[
    "Chick",
    "Chicken",
    "Cow",
    "Goat",
    "Horse",
    "Pig",
    "Sheep",
    "Duck",
    "Dog",
    "Cat",
    "Rabbit",
    "Goldfish",
    "Hamster",
    "Turtle",
    "Kitten",
    "Puppy",
    "Bear",
    "Moose",
    "Fox",
    "Raccoon",
    "Squirrel",
    "Owl",
    "Hedgehog",
    "Baby Penguin",
    "Penguin",
    "Arctic Fox",
    "Snowy Owl",
    "Polar Bear",
    "Arctic Hare",
    "Seal",
    "Walrus",
    "Tiger",
    "Panther",
    "Cockatoo",
    "Orangutan",
    "Anaconda",
    "Macaw",
    "Jaguar",
    "Capuchin",
    "Toucan",
    "Parrot",
    "Elf",
    "Witch",
    "Wizard",
    "Fairy",
    "Slime Monster",
    "Jester",
    "Dragon",
    "Unicorn",
    "Queen",
    "King",
    "Snow Globe",
    "Holiday Gift",
    "Hot Chocolate",
    "Gingerbread Man",
    "Gingerbread House",
    "Holiday Wreath",
    "Snowman",
    "Santa Claus",
    "Two of Spades",
    "Eat Me",
    "Drink Me",
    "Alice",
    "Queen of Hearts",
    "Dormouse",
    "White Rabbit",
    "Cheshire Cat",
    "Caterpillar",
    "Mad Hatter",
    "King of Hearts",
    "Toast",
    "Cereal",
    "Yogurt",
    "Breakfast Combo",
    "Orange Juice",
    "Milk",
    "Waffle",
    "Pancakes",
    "French Toast",
    "Pizza",
    "Sandwich",
    "Light Blue",
    "Black",
    "Red",
    "Purple",
    "Pink",
    "Orange",
    "Lime",
    "Green",
    "Teal",
    "Tan",
    "Maroon",
    "Gray",
    "Mint",
    "Salmon",
    "Burgandy",
    "Baby Blue",
    "Dust",
    "Brown",
    "Dull Blue",
    "Yellow",
    "Blue",
    "Pumpkin",
    "Swamp Monster",
    "Frankenstein",
    "Vampire",
    "Zombie",
    "Mummy",
    "Werewolf",
    "Ghost",
    "Spooky Pumpkin",
    "Spooky Mummy",
    "Spooky Ghost",
    "Toast",
    "Cereal",
    "Yogurt",
    "Orange Juice",
    "Milk",
    "Waffle",
    "Pancakes",
    "French Toast"
]
